Suddenly Explorers!
Suddenly explorers!
I'm Shihshinshin.
I'm Sakura Hinami.
Pleased to meet you.
We're here on a sudden expedition.
I'm not wearing my usual jersey today.
I'm wearing civilian clothes.
And if you look at the back...
Right now.
We're at the illumination of the Forest Garden Talas on the fourth floor of Evins.
We're at the illumination of the Forest Garden Talas on the 4th floor of Evins.
This year, it's a collaboration with Suddenly Talk.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
This oversized panel is here.
Please come with us.
Yes, but...
Today, in the Illumination Suddenly Talk collaboration...
I've asked you two to be photographers.
I'm going to introduce the places where you can enjoy the illumination.
I'll ask them to take various photos and introduce them to everyone watching.
Yes, I'll do that.
I understand.
Why do you look scared?
I'm not scared at all.
I see... you two are here in civilian clothes.
And this year, there are nine member colours.
The 4th floor has a zone for each member's colour, green for Shin, orange for Minano, etc.
That's why.
So let's go around there and take photos of the other two members.
Let's introduce them.
Okay.
Okay, first of all, Shin-san has the camera.
Okay, let's go Shin cameraman.
Let's take the first one, shall we?
Yes, I'll try.
First of all, let's use the signboard.
So this is where we are now.
So, two shots of hydrogen.
I feel like a member.
I'm going to take a picture of the day of the month.
Don't touch it.
I'm not allowed to touch you, not even on the board, because you've kissed a lot of people on the moon.
You've got a little bit of a stony mouth.
I see...
I see.
Oh, hearts?
It's got hearts in it.
But it might be difficult if you're not tall enough.
Oh, yeah, right there.
It's so cute.
So cute!
Wait, Shinji-san.
Are you taking a video?
Not a video?
No, no, it's a photo, no matter what.
No, it's a photo, no matter what.
I just thought something was wrong.
We don't have a photo.
You have a photo of yourself at Hinano's place, right?
I wanted to take a picture of it.
I thought it'd be funny if you took a picture of yourself.
The photographer's doing a lot of work, isn't he?
Okay, I'll take a picture.
Cheese!
You have to come with someone to take a picture, don't you?
That's right.
What about those who come alone? Hinano.
Those who come alone...
I think...
Or...
But it's great, isn't it, the oversized panel?
There it is.
Here you go.
Yeah, yeah.
We got a lot of good ones, didn't we?
Let's go see what colour they're in.
Let's see what colour they are.
Boo-boo, it's green here... a photo spot.
Why don't you take a picture of Pearl, Hirano?
Please do.
There are mushrooms here, too.
It's true.
There are indeed, and nine different kinds of mushrooms, too, according to colour.
Good, let's go! Company!
And good, good, good, like the snowdrops.
Like the one who discovered the snowdrops.
Like the one who discovered it.
It's a bit bright now, isn't it?
The world is...
The world is a little brighter now.
But it's really good.
It looks like it's on the new guy's Instagram.
It looks like it's going to be on a lot of Instagrams.
The girls got it, too, the girls.
The girls got one too.
It's like this!
What's up with that?
It's so good!
It's great!
It's like a date at the Green Nation, like a date...
I'm good with a camera... a battlefield camera.
No, you're not.
It's so cute.
Thank you very much.
It looks like it's on Instagram.
You're good?
Yeah, it's really good.
I put it on Instagram.
It's like...
Thank you very much.
This is the new mountain zone.
Let's take a walk.
If you go towards the pergola...
And here? What colour is this?
It's light blue.
Light blue.
Oh, there it is!
I've got it! I've got it!
It's fun to look for trees like this one.
You can take nine different photos.
There's a light blue zone, and when you get here, it turns red.
It's Kaja, isn't it?
There she is, in the most obvious place.
He's so hip-hop.
It's like Kaja.
This is cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
Glad you're here.
If you go through here...
Hero zone.
Yasumori-san's zone.
There he is.
Yasumori-san was here.
He's like a child of the earth.
Like a pastry shop.
If I collect them all, I'll become a Pretty Cure.
Why not? I'm sure it's true... the mushrooms are drinking mushroom juice... but the mushrooms are Kinaga's Just Cookie Mushrooms...
I'm sure it's just a bag of mushroom juice...
I'm going to do it with everyone!
I'm sure you've got the right idea...
It's white.
She's sleeping.
It's in keeping with the character.
Are you a sleepyhead?
I'm not a sleepyhead, but...
I'm not a character.
There's a white one here.
Here.
Here comes Hinano-san's zone. Orange. It's beautiful here, orange.
She's so full of energy.
Let's take a shot here, too.
Oh, that's good. Let's take a picture with this face.
Let's take a picture with this face, the same face as the mushrooms, the face they don't know they have.
That's the same face as the mushrooms.
He's doing it from a middle-to-upper angle.
He's getting into the new village.
I really like taking pictures.
He's cute.
You're happy when you get a good shot?
Yes, yes, yes. They're cute, so you take a lot of pictures of them. The type that gets upset? Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Would you take a lot of pictures?
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't stop my fingers.
You can't stop, can you?
But it's cold.
You're taking too many pictures.
Is it pink? Is that too much?
Is it pink? Is this Karen's zone? I like the pink lights.
This is pretty central, right here on the fourth floor, okay?
Let's go.
Can you get it like this? I see.
It's coming off.
You have to be careful, it can still get stuck.
If you hit it, it'll make it ache and they'll know.
It's not like that.
It's not like robbing a bank.
Oh, Yuna.
Cute.
Yuna zone.
Oh, I'm not a companion.
I'm your present?
There's alcohol in this box.
That's why it's a bit red.
I see. The blue Monappo is beautiful.
There's a zone with nine members like this, and mushrooms. And inside, there's this... that makes a certain sound every year.
This one.
I'll do the same with mine.
I'm going to ride it. That one?
Oh?
You're saying "mmm.
Mmm.
You're too light, aren't you? You weigh too much.
Right.
Maybe I am.
Listen to me.
It's good.
Um, yeah, listen, yeah, it's fine, although it was almost a live song.
That's how they were playing it, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess it's more like playing here than taking pictures.
It's cold, so move your body.
It's more like playing than taking pictures, isn't it? It's cold, so move your body.
Yes, so we enjoyed the illumination!
Yay!
Before the ending, a group of junior high school girls came and took photos in front of this oversized panel.
But I didn't really know them, but I knew them.
I'd be happy if I knew about it.
I'd be happy if you knew about it.
I'm sure we can do that... we can... we can... we can... we can... we can... we can do that... we can... we can... we can do that...
Nice, winter.
Every day from 16:00.
That's about right.
If you don't run late.
Who comes to wear it? Do you come here every day to wear it?
Oh, no?
It's automatic, probably.
Oh, it's automatic.
What's that?
New Year's, Valentine's Day, whispering?
I'd appreciate that.
Thank you!
I hope you all have a great time at all these events.
Such a gorgeous illumination.
Spend some time with Mr Tork!
So...
Thank you very much for today!
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!
Illumination! Illumination! Don't mind anyone! Bye-bye.